mybenefitwallet.com 2017-09-12

# Privacy Policy - BenefitWallet

## BenefitWallet Online Privacy Policy

### Introduction

This is the Online Privacy Policy of BenefitWallet in the United States.

This privacy policy covers the websites operated by BenefitWallet, a solution provided by Conduent HR Services, LLC (“BenefitWallet”, “we”, or “us”) in the United States.It also covers our online member and employer portals and a mobile application, BenefitWallet+.

At BenefitWallet, privacy on the Internet means that: 

  * BenefitWallet informs its website users (“you”) how it uses personally identifiable information that is collected online;
  * BenefitWallet maintains confidentiality and security safeguards for personally identifiable information; and
  * You have control over personally identifiable information you decide to submit to BenefitWallet.

BenefitWallet maintains the information it receives online in strict confidence; information you submit to BenefitWallet is not sold to or shared with third parties, except our subsidiaries, affiliates, agents and partners as described in this policy.

BenefitWallet reserves the right to notify you about administrative matters that pertain to your BenefitWallet products or services. We may disclose your personally identifiable information, as required by law or regulation, in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, or other legal action; or if BenefitWallet reasonably believes it is necessary to protect BenefitWallet, our customers, or the public. Although we do not currently anticipate a change in our corporate status, in the event of a merger or acquisition of the company that operates BenefitWallet or a substantial portion of its assets, BenefitWallet may disclose, transfer or sell personal information collected online to the surviving or acquiring party, respectively. Personal information collected online will remain subject to promises made in this Online Privacy Policy.

If you would like to contact BenefitWallet, you can reach BenefitWallet by emailing us at [info@mybenefitwallet.com](mailto:info@mybenefitwallet.com)

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy.

Privacy Complaints

BenefitWallet commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Inquiries or concerns regarding this privacy policy or other privacy issues should be directed to the Conduent Business Ethics and Compliance Office.

To report your inquiries or concerns to the Business Ethics and Compliance Office, please contact the Conduent Ethics Helpline. The Conduent Ethics Helpline is confidential and anonymous, if you so desire, and is available online and via a toll-free number listed below.

  * Web Reporting: [www.conduent.com/ethicshelpline](https://www.conduent.com/corporate-governance/ethics-helpline/)
  * US & Canada Toll-Free Number: 1-844-330-0221.
  * Direct Dial Toll-Free Numbers Outside US & Canada available at [www.conduent.com/ethics](https://www.conduent.com/ethics)

You may also contact us via postal mail at:  
BenefitWallet  
c/o Conduent Business Ethics and Compliance Office  
2828 N. Haskell Ave., Bldg.1 – 9th Floor  
Dallas, Texas 75204  
USA  

### Collection of Personally Identifiable Information

You may choose to give us personally identifiable information online to allow us to communicate with you or provide you with services. Our online forms ask for a small amount of relevant information, such as name, email, and employer name. The member portal requests information including, but not limited to, direct deposit information, such as bank, account, and routing numbers, which are passed on to other parties and are not stored by us. Information collected in the member portal and stored by us would include, but is not limited to, email and physical addresses, coverage levels, telephone numbers, alternate contacts, communications with you and user IDs and passwords. Some of this information may be passed on to third parties who perform services for us.

We may also collect information about your visits to our websites, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system, browser type and language, location information and details of your browsing patterns and communication data. This is more fully described under the section entitled “Cookies” below. We collect this information to determine such things as the number of visitors to various parts of our websites and to personalize your experience on our sites, and tailor our interactions with you.

Information collected and stored in the employer portal would include, but not be limited to, employee’s name, payroll information (such as employee and employer contributions), employer’s bank account information, profiles of persons with access to the employer’s portal (name, email and physical address, telephone numbers), and those persons’ user IDs and passwords. Employers can search the portals for their respective participants by fields which include, but may not be limited to, first and last names, SSNs, and payroll ID numbers, and search for when an account was opened and closed. The employer portal also has a function to send emails.

BenefitWallet does not direct its website or online services to children under 13 years old and does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.

Personally identifiable information collected is stored in the United States but may be accessed and processed in the United States or any other country in which Conduent or its subsidiaries, affiliates, agents or partners maintain facilities, and by using this website, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

The mobile native application automatically collects the IMEI number (or device number) of your mobile device so that we can uniquely identify your device.

**IMPORTANT NOTE:** If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for confidential personal information, do not respond. We will never request your user name, password, credit card information or other confidential personal information through email. 

### Why Does BenefitWallet Collect Personally Identifiable Information?

BenefitWallet uses personally identifiable information submitted online to: 

  * respond to your questions;
  * provide customer support;
  * share news, updates, or helpful tips about BenefitWallet products and services;
  * sign up for online services;
  * customize, analyze, and improve our products, services, technologies, communications and relationships with you; and
  * deliver products and services requested by you.

### Communication Preferences.

BenefitWallet may send email to you about services that may be of interest to you. 

### Security of Personally Identifiable Information

BenefitWallet maintains strict access control over personally identifiable information.

Only authorized BenefitWallet personnel, and those of our subsidiaries, affiliates, agents, and partners are allowed to handle information submitted to BenefitWallet online.

BenefitWallet’s websites and portals store personally identifiable information in password-protected environments on servers that are located in the United States. These servers are subject to Conduent’s information security policies, standards, and procedures.

Our agents and partners protect personally identifiable information.

When you arrange for services online from BenefitWallet it may be necessary to transfer personally identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliates, agents or partners, who then provide the services. BenefitWallet requires that its subsidiaries, affiliates, agents and partners handle personally identifiable information with the same concern for personal privacy as BenefitWallet.

### Access to Information

You may contact BenefitWallet to check the accuracy of your personally identifiable information or to request that your information be updated or deleted by calling 877-472-4200.

BenefitWallet reserves the right to confirm your identity.

### Cookies and Privacy Choices

What is a cookie?

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile device by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognize your device, letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improving your experience.

How does BenefitWallet use cookies?

BenefitWallet uses cookies to recognize repeat visits to our websites and to facilitate Web navigation. The cookies store your country and language, along with an assigned random session ID. In some cases, the cookies store name and address information so you do not have to re-enter this information in multiple forms.

The cookie information that BenefitWallet collects helps us track the number of visitors to our websites over time and determine whether these were new or repeat visits.

Can I block cookies?

Yes, the ability to enable, disable or delete cookies can be controlled though your website browser. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. Consult the “Help” menu of your browser application for details. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. If you block the use of cookies, you will not be able to use some of the features on BenefitWallet websites.

Links to non-BenefitWallet websites.

Other websites that may be accessed through our website, such as through links, may collect certain information about you through the use of cookies, web beacons and other features. We do not have access to or control over the cookies or other features that these third party sites may use, and the information practices of these third party websites are not covered by this Online Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

### Contact Us

We welcome questions or comments about our Online Privacy Policy. You may also contact us if you feel that your personal information is used in a way inconsistent with this policy. File a report using our Web submission tool on [www.conduent.com/ethics](https://www.conduent.com/ethics) or call 1-844-330-0221 if you are in North America. International numbers are available on [www.conduent.com/ethics](https://www.conduent.com/ethics).

You may also contact us via postal mail at:  
BenefitWallet  
c/o Conduent Business Ethics and Compliance Office  
2828 N. Haskell Ave., Bldg.1 – 9th Floor  
Dallas, Texas 75204  
USA  

If you have questions about BenefitWallet products or services, call us toll-free at 877-472-4200.

### Policy Updates

This policy may change from time to time. If we make changes, we will revise this Online Privacy Policy to reflect such changes and revise the effective date of the policy. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.
